Jonny Whittle

Curriculum Vitae

Introduction

Energetic and imaginative young web developer, who has an eye for great design and user experience and an attitude to succeed. From graduating The University of Bolton with a 2:1 degree in Graphic Design in 2020. I have taken on a Diploma in Software Development with Code Institute to enhance my skills ready for a career in the industry.

Experience

Jan 2022 -Present

Leigh Festival

Leigh Festival was created by me and my friend. With the aim of getting the community back together after Covid.

Key Responsibilities

- Create a simple to use website people could use to find all information about the festival.
- Manage a team of volunteers in planning and throughout the weekend.
- Create and manage social media and printed artwork e.g. Banners.

Key Achievements

- Over 1000 tickets sold online.
- Website had over 25,000 hits in total.

Oct 2020 -Present

Front End Developer

I created my own business to answer the question of how small pubs will manage with the table service only rule. I had to develop my skills in CSS, HTML and JS.

Me and a friend set out to create personalised table service websites, I focused on the UI and UX, whereas he worked on the back-end development.

Key Responsibilities

- Being able to sell the first prototype to our first client.
- To create an easy to use layout for both customers and staff.
- Work and manage my team to make sure we stuck to our deadlines.

I am continually looking for improvements, whether that be in the design or functionality of the websites.

Key Achievements

 Implemented new responsive system which increased sales by 22%.

Personal Info

Address

19 Beech Crescent, Leigh, WN7 3JL

Date of Birth

21.03.1999

Phone

07710811554

Email

Jonny.whittle@sky.com

Linked-in

linkedin.com/in/jonny-whittle

Portfolio

jonnywdev.github.io/Jonny Whittle/

Skills

Web Development

HTML CSS JAVASCRIPT Visual Studio Code Git Github Gitpod

Adobe

XD Illustrator InDesign Photoshop After Effects Premier Pro Lightroom

Other Programs

All Microsoft packages Google Sheets/Docs Cinema4D

Jonny Whittle

Curriculum Vitae

Experience

Jan 2021 -Present

Communications Director

Towards the start of 2021 I joined the board at my local rugby club. **Key Responsibilities**

- Increase our outreach on social media
- Bring people back into the pub.
- Communicate with my team and relay achievements and issues with the board.

Key Achievements

• 88.6% increase Facebook Page reach without using ads.

Education

School **Lowton Church of England High School** 2010-2015 8 GCSEs – A-Cs (including Maths & English)

College St John Rigby 6th Form College 2015-2018 3 AS Levels, 2 A Levels

University University of Bolton

2018-2020 BA (Hons) 2:1 Degree in Graphic Design

Postgraduate Code Institute

Course Postgraduate Course in Software Development 2018-2020

My Company

Avandor.co.uk

Other Roles

Morrisons, 2020 - Present

Customer Assistant I Doorstep Delivery I Click and Collect.

Impackt Design, Aug - Sept 2019

Graphic Design intern

Truth Design, June - Aug 2019

Graphic Design intern

Other Perks

- Friendly, great at communicating to customers.
- Graphic Design
 Degree, have an eye for good UX & UI design.
- In my free time I love to travel, I also play rugby union and golf.